那一天 那一瞬间 你就在我的身边
君はね　確かにあの時　私のそばにいた
不知疲倦 不知疲倦 不知疲倦地
いつだって　いつだって　いつだって
为我展露微笑  就算一度失去
すぐ横で笑っていた　無くしても
我也会找回 你的身影 绝不再松开 你的手心
取り戻す　君を I will never leave you
若你欲战，不妨跟我到街头巷外
If you wanna battle, then I'll take it to the street
那没有规则约束
Where there's no rules
摘下手套，请你入场
Take off the gloves ref, please step down
我将展现实力，你只是自投罗网
Gotta prove my skills so get down
我的轮转位移即将炸裂全场
My lyrical dempsey roll about to smack down now
将一击致命 令四座震惊
Gotta shoot to kill and shoot the skill
你无需害怕 只需遵循本心
Don't you be afraid, man's gotta do how it feels
六到七，至八九进十
Six to seven to eight to nine ten
看我扭转局面，让一切突破僵持
I flip the script to make it to the top ten, go
一夜无梦，时钟滴答作响
Dreamless dorm, ticking clock
我离开这个无声的房间
I walk away from the soundless room
无风之夜，月光好似融化
Windless night, moonlight melts
我的幽影陷入寒冷的黑暗
My ghostly shadow into the lukewarm gloom
在刀尖上随夜起舞
Nightly dance of bleeding swords
提醒自己依旧活着
Reminds me that I still live
每个人都在与恐惧对峙
Every man's gotta fight the fear
而我最先将其证实
I'm the first to admit it
锐利的信念开辟全新的世代
Sheer thoughts provoke the new era
我令人望而却步，而唯一的对手却是我的阴影
Become a big terror, but my only rival is my shadow
回头重来，这次彻底搞定我的麻烦
Rewind then play it back and fix my own error
低身广躯，一切都在好转
Get low to the ground, it's getting better
就如我告诉过你：日积月累，冷静面对
Like I told you before, double up, I did bone chiller
从L到J，紧紧抓住羁绊，打出手中的手牌B
L to the J, say stay laced, here's my card, B
皇家同花顺，而我正是那张王牌
Royal flush and I'm the ace